A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "OBESITY: A Nasal decongestant and a local anesthetic for weight control" Reprints, 21:65, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 457, Folder 316)
- "OBESITY: A Nasal decongestant and a local anesthetic for weight control" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:65, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 457, Folder 317)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:66, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 458, Folder 318)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:66, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 458, Folder 319)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea" Sources: "Check Copy" 21:66, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 458, Folder 320)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea" Original Manuscript, 21:66, 1979 Aug. 10 (Box 458, Folder 321)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:66, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 322)
- "DIALYSIS: Home peritoneal dialysis for-stage renal disease" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:69, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 323)
- "DIALYSIS: Home peritoneal dialysis for-stage renal disease" Original Manuscript, 21:69, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 324)
- "DIALYSIS: Home peritoneal dialysis for-stage renal disease" Reprints, 21:69, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 325)
- "DIALYSIS: Home peritoneal dialysis for-stage renal disease" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:69, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 326)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 327)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 328)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 458, Folder 329)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children" Adverse Effects, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 459, Folder 330)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children"' Original Manuscript, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 459, Folder 331)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children" Reprints, 21:70, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 459, Folder 332)
- "MALARIA: Chemoprophylasis of Chloroquine resistant malaria: an additional note." Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:72, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 459, Folder 333)
- "MALARIA: Chemoprophylasis of Chloroquine resistant malaria: an additional note." Original Manuscript, 21:72, 1979 Aug. 24 (Box 459, Folder 334)
- "MALARIA: Chemoprophylasis of Chloroquine resistant malaria: an additional note." Reprints, 21:72, 1979 September 7 (Box 459, Folder 335)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 459, Folder 336)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 459, Folder 337)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 459, Folder 338)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Original Manuscript, 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 460, Folder 339)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Reprints, 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 460, Folder 340)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery" Reprints, 21:73, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 341)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 342)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 343)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches" Original Manuscript, 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 344)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches" Reprints, 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 345)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 346)
- "LITHIUM: Lithium for cluster headache" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:78, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 347)
- "LITHIUM: Lithium for cluster headache" Manufacturers? Replies, 21:78, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 348)
- "LITHIUM: Lithium for cluster headache" Original Manuscript, 21:78, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 349)
- "LITHIUM: Lithium for cluster headache" Reprints, 21:78, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 350)
- "EYE DISEASE: Natamycin for keratomycosis" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:79, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 351)
- "EYE DISEASE: Natamycin for keratomycosis" Original Manuscript, 21:79, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 352)
- "EYE DISEASE: Natamycin for keratomycosis" Reprints, 21:79, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 353)
- "EYE DISEASE: Natamycin for keratomycosis" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:79, 1979 October 5 (Box 461, Folder 354)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 461, Folder 355)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 461, Folder 356)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 357)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Original Manuscript, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 358)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Reprints, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 359)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Reprints, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 360)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal" Advertising: Package Inserts, 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 361)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:83, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 362)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:83, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 363)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine" Original Manuscript, 21:83, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 364)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine" Reprints, 21:83, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 365)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:83, 1979 October 19 (Box 462, Folder 366)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 367)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 367A)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Manufacturers? Replies, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 368)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Tables, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 369)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Original Manuscript, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 370)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Reprints, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 371)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 372)
- "ANGINA PECTORIS: Oral isosorbide dinitrate for angina" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:88, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 373)
- "ANGINA PECTORIS: Oral isosorbide dinitrate for angina" Original Manuscript, 21:88, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 374)
- "ANGINA PECTORIS: Oral isosorbide dinitrate for angina" Reprints, 21:88, 1979 October 19 (Box 464, Folder 375)
- "ANGINA PECTORIS: Oral isosorbide dinitrate for angina" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:88, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 376)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 377)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 378)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)" Manufacturers? Replies, 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 379)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)" Original Manuscript, 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 380)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)" Reprints, 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 381)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 382)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 383)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate" Original Manuscript, 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 384)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate" Reprints, 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 385)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 386)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:91, 1979 November 2 (Box 465, Folder 387)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:91, 1979 November 2 (Box 465, Folder 388)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children" Original Manuscript, 21:91, 1979 November 2 (Box 465, Folder 389)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children" Reprints, 21:91, 1979 November 2 (Box 465, Folder 390)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:91, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 391)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 392)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 393)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Sources: "Check Copy" 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 394)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Original Manuscript, 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 395)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Reprints, 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 396)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Reprints, 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 466, Folder 397)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products" Reprints, 21:93, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 398)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 399)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 400)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment" Original Manuscript, 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 401)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment" Reprints, 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 402)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 403)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 404)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose" Original Manuscript, 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 405)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 406)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose" Reprints, 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 407)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 408)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:100, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 409)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:100, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 410)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal" Original Manuscript, 21:100, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 411)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal" Reprints, 21:100, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 412)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:100, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 413)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 414)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction" Original Manuscript, 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 415)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction" Reprints, 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 416)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction" Reprints, 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 417)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 418)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 419)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 420)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults" Original Manuscript, 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 421)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults" Reprints, 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 422)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 423)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:104, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 424)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:104, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 425)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies" Original Manuscript, 21:104, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 426)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies" Reprints, 21:104, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 427)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies" 21:104, 1979 December 28 (Box 468, Folder 428)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 429)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 429)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 430)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 431)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Original Manuscript, 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 432)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Sources: "Check Copy", 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 433)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections" Reprints, 21:105, 1980 January 11 (Box 469, Folder 434)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 435)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)" Original Manuscript, 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 436)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)" Reprints, 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 437)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)" Reprints, 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 438)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)" Advertising: Package Insert, 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 439)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 440)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 441)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation" Original Manuscript, 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 442)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation" Reprints, 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 443)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation" Advertising: Package Insert, 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 444)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:4, 1980 January 11 (Box 471, Folder 445)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:4, 1980 January 11 (Box 471, Folder 446)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching" Original Manuscript, 22:4, 1980 January 11 (Box 471, Folder 447)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching" Reprints, 22:4, 1980 January 11 (Box 471, Folder 448)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching" Advertising: Package Insert, 22:4, 1980 January 25 (Box 471, Folder 449)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 471, Folder 450)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 471, Folder 451)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 471, Folder 452)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 472, Folder 453)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Adverse Effects, 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 472, Folder 454)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Sources: "Check Copy", 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 472, Folder 455)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs" Reprints, 22:5, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 456)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:13, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 457)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:13, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 458)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Adverse Effects, 22:13, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 459)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Original Manuscript, 22:13, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 460)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Reprints, 22:13, 1980 Feb. 8 (Box 472, Folder 461)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin" Advertising: Package Insert, 22:13, 1980 February 8 (Box 472, Folder 462)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 472, Folder 463)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension" Sources: "Check Copy", 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 472, Folder 464)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension" Original Manuscript, 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 465)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension" Reprints, 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 466)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension" Reprints, 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 467)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 468)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 469)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Sources; "Check Copy" 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 470)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted from scholarly access.
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 471)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Reprints, 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 472)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant" Advertising: Package- Insert, 22:16, 1980 February 22 (Box 473, Folder 473)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 473, Folder 474)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 473, Folder 475)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 476)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 477)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Adverse Effects, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 478)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Original Manuscript, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 479)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Reprints, 22:17, February 22, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 480)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium" Reprints, 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 481)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 482)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 475, Folder 483)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Original Manuscript, 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 475, Folder 484)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Sources; "Check Copy", 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 475, Folder 485)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Reprints, 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 475, Folder 486)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity" Reprints 22:19, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 487)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 488)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Manufacturers' Replies, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 489)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Original Manuscript, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 490)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Sources; "Check Copy", 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 491)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 492)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 493)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 476, Folder 494)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 476, Folder 495)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 476, Folder 496)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)" Reprints, 22:21, 1980 March 21 (Box 476, Folder 497)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction" Consultants: ML Drafts, 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 476, Folder 498)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction" Adverse Effects, 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 476, Folder 499)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction" Original Manuscript, 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 477, Folder 500)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction" Sources; "Check Copy", 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 477, Folder 501)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction" Reprints, 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 477, Folder 502)